[
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "abogado",
    "back": "lawyer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "lawyer",
    "back": "abogado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "abrazar",
    "back": "to cuddle/embrace",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to cuddle/embrace",
    "back": "abrazar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "abuela",
    "back": "Grandmother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Grandmother",
    "back": "abuela",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "abuelo",
    "back": "Grandfather",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Grandfather",
    "back": "abuelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "aficiones",
    "back": "hobbies",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "hobbies",
    "back": "aficiones",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "afuera",
    "back": "outside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "outside",
    "back": "afuera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "agua",
    "back": "water",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "water",
    "back": "agua",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "alto",
    "back": "tall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "tall",
    "back": "alto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "amigos",
    "back": "friends",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "friends",
    "back": "amigos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "animales",
    "back": "animals",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "animals",
    "back": "animales",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "años",
    "back": "years",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "years",
    "back": "años",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "aprender",
    "back": "to learn",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to learn",
    "back": "aprender",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "arbol",
    "back": "tree",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "tree",
    "back": "arbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "arena",
    "back": "sand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "sand",
    "back": "arena",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ayudar",
    "back": "to help",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to help",
    "back": "ayudar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "bajo",
    "back": "short",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "short",
    "back": "bajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "barba",
    "back": "beard",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "beard",
    "back": "barba",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "beber",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "beber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "bebida",
    "back": "drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "drink",
    "back": "bebida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "bonito",
    "back": "pretty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "pretty",
    "back": "bonito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "botella",
    "back": "bottle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "bottle",
    "back": "botella",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "bueno",
    "back": "good",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "good",
    "back": "bueno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "buscar",
    "back": "to search for/ to look for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to search for/ to look for",
    "back": "buscar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "café",
    "back": "coffee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "coffee",
    "back": "café",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "cafetería",
    "back": "coffee shop",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "coffee shop",
    "back": "cafetería",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "calle",
    "back": "street",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "street",
    "back": "calle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "caminar",
    "back": "to walk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to walk",
    "back": "caminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "cansado",
    "back": "tired",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "tired",
    "back": "cansado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "carne",
    "back": "meat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "meat",
    "back": "carne",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "casa",
    "back": "house",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "house",
    "back": "casa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "castillo",
    "back": "castle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "castle",
    "back": "castillo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "cenar",
    "back": "to have dinner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to have dinner",
    "back": "cenar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "chocolate",
    "back": "chocolate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "chocolate",
    "back": "chocolate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ciencia ficción",
    "back": "Science fiction",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Science fiction",
    "back": "ciencia ficción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "claro",
    "back": "of course/ sure",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "of course/ sure",
    "back": "claro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "cola",
    "back": "tail",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "tail",
    "back": "cola",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "coche",
    "back": "car",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "car",
    "back": "coche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "cocinar",
    "back": "to cook",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to cook",
    "back": "cocinar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "comer",
    "back": "to eat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to eat",
    "back": "comer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "comida",
    "back": "food",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "food",
    "back": "comida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "como",
    "back": "how/like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "how/like",
    "back": "como",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "comprar",
    "back": "to buy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to buy",
    "back": "comprar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "con",
    "back": "with",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "with",
    "back": "con",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "conducir",
    "back": "to drive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to drive",
    "back": "conducir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "correr",
    "back": "to run",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to run",
    "back": "correr",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "decir",
    "back": "to say",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to say",
    "back": "decir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "deportes",
    "back": "sports",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "sports",
    "back": "deportes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "desayunar",
    "back": "to have breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to have breakfast",
    "back": "desayunar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "día",
    "back": "day",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "day",
    "back": "día",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "domingo",
    "back": "Sunday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Sunday",
    "back": "domingo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "donde",
    "back": "where",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "where",
    "back": "donde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "dificil",
    "back": "difficult",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "difficult",
    "back": "dificil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "dormir",
    "back": "to sleep",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to sleep",
    "back": "dormir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ducharse",
    "back": "to shower",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to shower",
    "back": "ducharse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "empezar",
    "back": "to start",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to start",
    "back": "empezar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "en",
    "back": "in",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "in",
    "back": "en",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "encontrar",
    "back": "to find",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to find",
    "back": "encontrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "escuchar",
    "back": "to listen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to listen",
    "back": "escuchar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "español",
    "back": "Spanish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Spanish",
    "back": "español",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "especialmente",
    "back": "especially",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "especially",
    "back": "especialmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "estanque",
    "back": "pond",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "pond",
    "back": "estanque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "estar",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "estar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "estudiar",
    "back": "to study",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to study",
    "back": "estudiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "familia",
    "back": "family",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "family",
    "back": "familia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "fin de semana",
    "back": "weekend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "weekend",
    "back": "fin de semana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "francés",
    "back": "French",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "French",
    "back": "francés",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "happy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "feliz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "fresa",
    "back": "strawberry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "strawberry",
    "back": "fresa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "fumar",
    "back": "to smoke",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to smoke",
    "back": "fumar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "fútbol",
    "back": "football",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "football",
    "back": "fútbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "gato",
    "back": "cat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "cat",
    "back": "gato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "grande",
    "back": "big",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "big",
    "back": "grande",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "gritar",
    "back": "to shout",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to shout",
    "back": "gritar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "guapo",
    "back": "pretty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "pretty",
    "back": "guapo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "gustar",
    "back": "to like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to like",
    "back": "gustar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "habitación",
    "back": "room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "room",
    "back": "habitación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "hablar",
    "back": "to speak",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to speak",
    "back": "hablar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "helado",
    "back": "ice cream",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "ice cream",
    "back": "helado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "hermano",
    "back": "brother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "brother",
    "back": "hermano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "histroric",
    "back": "history",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "history",
    "back": "histroric",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "hombre",
    "back": "man",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "man",
    "back": "hombre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "hongos",
    "back": "mushrooms",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "mushrooms",
    "back": "hongos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "huevos",
    "back": "eggs",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "eggs",
    "back": "huevos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "idioma",
    "back": "language",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "language",
    "back": "idioma",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "igualmente",
    "back": "you too/equally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "you too/equally",
    "back": "igualmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ilegal",
    "back": "Ilegal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Ilegal",
    "back": "ilegal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "información",
    "back": "information",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "information",
    "back": "información",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "inglés",
    "back": "English",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "English",
    "back": "inglés",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "italiano",
    "back": "Italian",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Italian",
    "back": "italiano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "jardín",
    "back": "garden",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "garden",
    "back": "jardín",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "jefe",
    "back": "boss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "boss",
    "back": "jefe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "jugar",
    "back": "to play",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to play",
    "back": "jugar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "juegos",
    "back": "games",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "games",
    "back": "juegos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "junto",
    "back": "together",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "together",
    "back": "junto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "llamar",
    "back": "to call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to call",
    "back": "llamar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "leche",
    "back": "milk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "milk",
    "back": "leche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "leer",
    "back": "to read",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to read",
    "back": "leer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "levantar",
    "back": "to get up",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to get up",
    "back": "levantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "libros",
    "back": "books",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "books",
    "back": "libros",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "madre",
    "back": "mother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "mother",
    "back": "madre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "maestro",
    "back": "teacher",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "teacher",
    "back": "maestro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "más",
    "back": "more",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "more",
    "back": "más",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mascota",
    "back": "pet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "pet",
    "back": "mascota",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mensaje",
    "back": "message",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "message",
    "back": "mensaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mesa",
    "back": "table",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "table",
    "back": "mesa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mientras",
    "back": "while",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "while",
    "back": "mientras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mirar",
    "back": "to look at/ to watch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to look at/ to watch",
    "back": "mirar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mono",
    "back": "monkey",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "monkey",
    "back": "mono",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho",
    "back": "many/ a lot of",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "many/ a lot of",
    "back": "mucho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho gusto",
    "back": "nice to meet you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "nice to meet you",
    "back": "mucho gusto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mujer",
    "back": "woman",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "woman",
    "back": "mujer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "mundo",
    "back": "world",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "world",
    "back": "mundo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "música",
    "back": "music",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "music",
    "back": "música",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "muy",
    "back": "very",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "very",
    "back": "muy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "naranja",
    "back": "orange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "orange",
    "back": "naranja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "nariz",
    "back": "nose",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "nose",
    "back": "nariz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "necesitar",
    "back": "to need",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to need",
    "back": "necesitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "negro",
    "back": "black",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "black",
    "back": "negro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "niños",
    "back": "children",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "children",
    "back": "niños",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "noche",
    "back": "night",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "night",
    "back": "noche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "normalmente",
    "back": "normally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "normally",
    "back": "normalmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "oficina",
    "back": "office",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "office",
    "back": "oficina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ojos",
    "back": "eyes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "eyes",
    "back": "ojos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pagar",
    "back": "to pay",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to pay",
    "back": "pagar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "parque",
    "back": "park",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "park",
    "back": "parque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pasar",
    "back": "to pass/spend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to pass/spend",
    "back": "pasar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "país",
    "back": "country",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "country",
    "back": "país",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "películas",
    "back": "films",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "films",
    "back": "películas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pelo",
    "back": "hair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "hair",
    "back": "pelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pensar",
    "back": "to think",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to think",
    "back": "pensar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pequeña",
    "back": "small",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "small",
    "back": "pequeña",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "periodico",
    "back": "newspaper",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "newspaper",
    "back": "periodico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pero",
    "back": "but",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "but",
    "back": "pero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "personas",
    "back": "people",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "people",
    "back": "personas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pescado",
    "back": "fish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "fish",
    "back": "pescado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pies",
    "back": "feet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "feet",
    "back": "pies",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "piso",
    "back": "floor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "floor",
    "back": "piso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "plátano",
    "back": "banana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "banana",
    "back": "plátano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "playa",
    "back": "beach",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "beach",
    "back": "playa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "poder",
    "back": "to be able to",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to be able to",
    "back": "poder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "pollo",
    "back": "chicken",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "chicken",
    "back": "pollo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "por ejemplo",
    "back": "for example",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "for example",
    "back": "por ejemplo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "por favor",
    "back": "please",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "please",
    "back": "por favor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "por qué",
    "back": "why",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "why",
    "back": "por qué",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "preocupado/a",
    "back": "worried",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "worried",
    "back": "preocupado/a",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "preguntar",
    "back": "to ask",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to ask",
    "back": "preguntar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "propio",
    "back": "own",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "own",
    "back": "propio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "querer",
    "back": "to want",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to want",
    "back": "querer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "raro",
    "back": "rare/strange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "rare/strange",
    "back": "raro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "recibir",
    "back": "to receive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to receive",
    "back": "recibir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "recate",
    "back": "rescue",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "rescue",
    "back": "recate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "reír",
    "back": "to laugh",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to laugh",
    "back": "reír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "responder",
    "back": "to respond/answer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to respond/answer",
    "back": "responder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "revistas",
    "back": "magazines",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "magazines",
    "back": "revistas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sábado",
    "back": "Saturday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Saturday",
    "back": "sábado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "salgar",
    "back": "to go out",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to go out",
    "back": "salgar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "salvar",
    "back": "to save",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to save",
    "back": "salvar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "secreto",
    "back": "secret",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "secret",
    "back": "secreto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "seguro",
    "back": "sure",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "sure",
    "back": "seguro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sentarse",
    "back": "to sit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to sit",
    "back": "sentarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "serioso",
    "back": "serious",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "serious",
    "back": "serioso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sí",
    "back": "yes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "yes",
    "back": "sí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sillas",
    "back": "chairs",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "chairs",
    "back": "sillas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sombrilla",
    "back": "beach umbrella",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "beach umbrella",
    "back": "sombrilla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "sonreír",
    "back": "to smile",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to smile",
    "back": "sonreír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "supermercado",
    "back": "supermarket",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "supermarket",
    "back": "supermercado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "también",
    "back": "also",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "also",
    "back": "también",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "té",
    "back": "tea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "tea",
    "back": "té",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "television",
    "back": "television",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "television",
    "back": "television",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "tener",
    "back": "to have",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to have",
    "back": "tener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "terminar",
    "back": "to end",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to end",
    "back": "terminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "típico",
    "back": "typical",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "typical",
    "back": "típico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "tipo",
    "back": "type",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "type",
    "back": "tipo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "todos",
    "back": "all",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "all",
    "back": "todos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajar",
    "back": "to work",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to work",
    "back": "trabajar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajo",
    "back": "job",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "job",
    "back": "trabajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "tradicional",
    "back": "traditional",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "traditional",
    "back": "tradicional",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "triste",
    "back": "sad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "triste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "usar",
    "back": "to use",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to use",
    "back": "usar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "visitar",
    "back": "to visit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to visit",
    "back": "visitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "vivir",
    "back": "to live",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "vivir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "ver",
    "back": "to see",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "ver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "verde",
    "back": "green",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "green",
    "back": "verde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "veteneria",
    "back": "Vet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "Vet",
    "back": "veteneria",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "voy",
    "back": "to go",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "to go",
    "back": "voy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Recognition",
    "front": "zumo",
    "back": "juice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?::Production",
    "front": "juice",
    "back": "zumo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::1 - ¿Dondé Está Maurice?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "a veces",
    "back": "sometimes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "sometimes",
    "back": "a veces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "abrazar",
    "back": "to hug/cuddle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to hug/cuddle",
    "back": "abrazar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "abrir",
    "back": "to open",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to open",
    "back": "abrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "aceite",
    "back": "oil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "oil",
    "back": "aceite",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "adentro",
    "back": "inside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "inside",
    "back": "adentro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "ahora",
    "back": "now",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "now",
    "back": "ahora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "algo",
    "back": "something",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "something",
    "back": "algo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "allí",
    "back": "there",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "there",
    "back": "allí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "alto",
    "back": "tall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "tall",
    "back": "alto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "amante",
    "back": "lover",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "lover",
    "back": "amante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "amarillo",
    "back": "yellow",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "yellow",
    "back": "amarillo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "amigo",
    "back": "friend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "friend",
    "back": "amigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "año",
    "back": "year",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "year",
    "back": "año",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "aquí",
    "back": "here",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "here",
    "back": "aquí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "árbol",
    "back": "tree",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "tree",
    "back": "árbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "bailar",
    "back": "to dance",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to dance",
    "back": "bailar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "bajo",
    "back": "short",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "short",
    "back": "bajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "balcón",
    "back": "balcony",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "balcony",
    "back": "balcón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "baloncesto",
    "back": "basketball",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "basketball",
    "back": "baloncesto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "banco",
    "back": "bank",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bank",
    "back": "banco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "baño",
    "back": "bathroom/bath",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bathroom/bath",
    "back": "baño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "barbacoa",
    "back": "BBQ",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "BBQ",
    "back": "barbacoa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "barrio",
    "back": "neighbourhood",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "neighbourhood",
    "back": "barrio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "beber",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "beber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "besar",
    "back": "to kiss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to kiss",
    "back": "besar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "bonito",
    "back": "pretty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "pretty",
    "back": "bonito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "brillante",
    "back": "shiny",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "shiny",
    "back": "brillante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "burbuja",
    "back": "bubble",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bubble",
    "back": "burbuja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cada",
    "back": "each",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "each",
    "back": "cada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "café",
    "back": "coffee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "coffee",
    "back": "café",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "caja",
    "back": "box",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "box",
    "back": "caja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "campo",
    "back": "countryside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "countryside",
    "back": "campo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cansado",
    "back": "tired",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "tired",
    "back": "cansado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cantar",
    "back": "to sing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to sing",
    "back": "cantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cama",
    "back": "bed",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bed",
    "back": "cama",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "carne",
    "back": "meat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "meat",
    "back": "carne",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "casa",
    "back": "house",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "house",
    "back": "casa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cena",
    "back": "dinner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "dinner",
    "back": "cena",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cepillar",
    "back": "to comb",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to comb",
    "back": "cepillar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cerca",
    "back": "near",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "near",
    "back": "cerca",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cinco",
    "back": "five",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "five",
    "back": "cinco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cine",
    "back": "cinema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "cinema",
    "back": "cine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "coche",
    "back": "car",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "car",
    "back": "coche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cocina",
    "back": "kitchen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "kitchen",
    "back": "cocina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cocinar",
    "back": "to cook",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to cook",
    "back": "cocinar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cocinero",
    "back": "cook",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "cook",
    "back": "cocinero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "conducir",
    "back": "to drive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to drive",
    "back": "conducir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cuatro",
    "back": "four",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "four",
    "back": "cuatro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "comenzar",
    "back": "to start",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to start",
    "back": "comenzar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "comer",
    "back": "to eat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to eat",
    "back": "comer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "comida",
    "back": "food",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "food",
    "back": "comida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "con",
    "back": "with",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "with",
    "back": "con",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "contiene",
    "back": "contains",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "contains",
    "back": "contiene",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "copa",
    "back": "cup",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "cup",
    "back": "copa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "correr",
    "back": "to run",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to run",
    "back": "correr",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "cortar",
    "back": "to cut",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to cut",
    "back": "cortar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "corto",
    "back": "short",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "short",
    "back": "corto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "crimen",
    "back": "crime",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "crime",
    "back": "crimen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "dálmata",
    "back": "Dalmatian",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "Dalmatian",
    "back": "dálmata",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "of",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "of",
    "back": "de",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "de nuevo",
    "back": "again",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "again",
    "back": "de nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "de repente",
    "back": "suddenly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "suddenly",
    "back": "de repente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "decir",
    "back": "to say",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to say",
    "back": "decir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "delgado",
    "back": "slim",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "slim",
    "back": "delgado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "deportes",
    "back": "sports",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "sports",
    "back": "deportes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "después",
    "back": "after",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "after",
    "back": "después",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "desayunar",
    "back": "to eat breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to eat breakfast",
    "back": "desayunar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "desayuno",
    "back": "breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "breakfast",
    "back": "desayuno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "detalles",
    "back": "details",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "details",
    "back": "detalles",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "día",
    "back": "day",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "day",
    "back": "día",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "diez",
    "back": "ten",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "ten",
    "back": "diez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "discusión",
    "back": "argument/discussion",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "argument/discussion",
    "back": "discusión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "divertido",
    "back": "funny",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "funny",
    "back": "divertido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "doctora",
    "back": "doctor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "doctor",
    "back": "doctora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "dormir",
    "back": "to sleep",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to sleep",
    "back": "dormir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "dos",
    "back": "two",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "two",
    "back": "dos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "elegante",
    "back": "elegant",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "elegant",
    "back": "elegante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "empezar",
    "back": "to start",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to start",
    "back": "empezar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "en",
    "back": "in",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "in",
    "back": "en",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "enfermedad",
    "back": "illness",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "illness",
    "back": "enfermedad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "enorme",
    "back": "enormous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "enormous",
    "back": "enorme",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "entender",
    "back": "to understand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to understand",
    "back": "entender",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "escribir",
    "back": "to write",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to write",
    "back": "escribir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "escuchar",
    "back": "to listen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to listen",
    "back": "escuchar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "espacio",
    "back": "space",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "space",
    "back": "espacio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "españa",
    "back": "Spain",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "Spain",
    "back": "españa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "especialmente",
    "back": "especially",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "especially",
    "back": "especialmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "estanque",
    "back": "pond",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "pond",
    "back": "estanque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "este",
    "back": "this",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "this",
    "back": "este",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "excelente",
    "back": "excellent",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "excellent",
    "back": "excelente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "familia",
    "back": "family",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "family",
    "back": "familia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "favorito",
    "back": "favourite",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "favourite",
    "back": "favorito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "happy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "feliz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "fin de semana",
    "back": "weekend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "weekend",
    "back": "fin de semana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "fruta",
    "back": "fruit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "fruit",
    "back": "fruta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "fútbol",
    "back": "football",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "football",
    "back": "fútbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "futuro",
    "back": "future",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "future",
    "back": "futuro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "gracias",
    "back": "thank you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "thank you",
    "back": "gracias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "grande",
    "back": "big",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "big",
    "back": "grande",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "gritar",
    "back": "to shout",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to shout",
    "back": "gritar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "guapo",
    "back": "handsome",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "handsome",
    "back": "guapo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "gustar",
    "back": "to like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to like",
    "back": "gustar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "habitaciones",
    "back": "rooms",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "rooms",
    "back": "habitaciones",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hace buen tiempo",
    "back": "nice weather",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "nice weather",
    "back": "hace buen tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hacer",
    "back": "to do",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to do",
    "back": "hacer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hay",
    "back": "there is/are",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "there is/are",
    "back": "hay",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hermano",
    "back": "brother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "brother",
    "back": "hermano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hija",
    "back": "daughter",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "daughter",
    "back": "hija",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "historias",
    "back": "stories",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "stories",
    "back": "historias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "hospital",
    "back": "hospital",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "hospital",
    "back": "hospital",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "inglaterra",
    "back": "England",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "England",
    "back": "inglaterra",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "interesante",
    "back": "interesting",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "interesting",
    "back": "interesante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "jardín",
    "back": "garden",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "garden",
    "back": "jardín",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "jueves",
    "back": "thursday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "thursday",
    "back": "jueves",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "jugar",
    "back": "play",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "play",
    "back": "jugar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "junto",
    "back": "together",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "together",
    "back": "junto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "labio",
    "back": "lip",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "lip",
    "back": "labio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "largo",
    "back": "long",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "long",
    "back": "largo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "leer",
    "back": "to read",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to read",
    "back": "leer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "lejos",
    "back": "far",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "far",
    "back": "lejos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "libre",
    "back": "free",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "free",
    "back": "libre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "libro",
    "back": "book",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "book",
    "back": "libro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "llamar",
    "back": "to call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to call",
    "back": "llamar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "llegar",
    "back": "to arrive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to arrive",
    "back": "llegar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "llevar",
    "back": "to wear",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to wear",
    "back": "llevar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "llorar",
    "back": "to cry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to cry",
    "back": "llorar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "luego",
    "back": "then",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "then",
    "back": "luego",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "llueve",
    "back": "it rains",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "it rains",
    "back": "llueve",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "madre",
    "back": "mother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "mother",
    "back": "madre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "maleta",
    "back": "suitcase",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "suitcase",
    "back": "maleta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "máquina",
    "back": "machine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "machine",
    "back": "máquina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "marrón",
    "back": "brown",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "brown",
    "back": "marrón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "martes",
    "back": "tuesday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "tuesday",
    "back": "martes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "media",
    "back": "half",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "half",
    "back": "media",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "medico",
    "back": "doctor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "doctor",
    "back": "medico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mejor",
    "back": "best",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "best",
    "back": "mejor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mensaje",
    "back": "message",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "message",
    "back": "mensaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mexicano",
    "back": "Mexican",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "Mexican",
    "back": "mexicano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "méxico",
    "back": "Mexico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "Mexico",
    "back": "méxico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mientras",
    "back": "while",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "while",
    "back": "mientras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "minuto",
    "back": "minute",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "minute",
    "back": "minuto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mío",
    "back": "mine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "mine",
    "back": "mío",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mirar",
    "back": "to look",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to look",
    "back": "mirar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "moderno",
    "back": "modern",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "modern",
    "back": "moderno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho",
    "back": "many",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "many",
    "back": "mucho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "muerta",
    "back": "dead",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "dead",
    "back": "muerta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "música",
    "back": "music",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "music",
    "back": "música",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "muy",
    "back": "very",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "very",
    "back": "muy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "nadar",
    "back": "to swim",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to swim",
    "back": "nadar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "nariz",
    "back": "nose",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "nose",
    "back": "nariz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "necesitar",
    "back": "to need",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to need",
    "back": "necesitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "negro",
    "back": "black",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "black",
    "back": "negro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "nervioso",
    "back": "nervous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "nervous",
    "back": "nervioso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "noticias",
    "back": "news",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "news",
    "back": "noticias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "nueve",
    "back": "nine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "nine",
    "back": "nueve",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "ocho",
    "back": "eight",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "eight",
    "back": "ocho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "ojo",
    "back": "eyes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "eyes",
    "back": "ojo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "opción",
    "back": "option",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "option",
    "back": "opción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "padre",
    "back": "father",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "father",
    "back": "padre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pájaro",
    "back": "bird",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bird",
    "back": "pájaro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pan",
    "back": "bread",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "bread",
    "back": "pan",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "papa",
    "back": "potato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "potato",
    "back": "papa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "para",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "para",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pareja",
    "back": "couple",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "couple",
    "back": "pareja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "parque",
    "back": "park",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "park",
    "back": "parque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pasar",
    "back": "pass",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "pass",
    "back": "pasar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pelo",
    "back": "hair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "hair",
    "back": "pelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pendiente",
    "back": "earring",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "earring",
    "back": "pendiente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pena",
    "back": "shame/pity",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "shame/pity",
    "back": "pena",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "pequeño",
    "back": "small",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "small",
    "back": "pequeño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "periódico",
    "back": "newspaper",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "newspaper",
    "back": "periódico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "perro",
    "back": "dog",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "dog",
    "back": "perro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "piano",
    "back": "piano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "piano",
    "back": "piano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "piscina",
    "back": "swimming pool",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "swimming pool",
    "back": "piscina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "piso",
    "back": "floor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "floor",
    "back": "piso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "planta",
    "back": "plant",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "plant",
    "back": "planta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "playa",
    "back": "beach",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "beach",
    "back": "playa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "poner",
    "back": "to put",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to put",
    "back": "poner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "por favor",
    "back": "please",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "please",
    "back": "por favor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "por supuesto",
    "back": "of course",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "of course",
    "back": "por supuesto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "porque",
    "back": "because",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "because",
    "back": "porque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "primavera",
    "back": "spring",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "spring",
    "back": "primavera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "privacidad",
    "back": "privacy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "privacy",
    "back": "privacidad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "preferir",
    "back": "to prefer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to prefer",
    "back": "preferir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "próximo",
    "back": "next",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "next",
    "back": "próximo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "puerta",
    "back": "door",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "door",
    "back": "puerta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "que",
    "back": "what",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "what",
    "back": "que",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "quien",
    "back": "who",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "who",
    "back": "quien",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "quitar",
    "back": "to take off",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to take off",
    "back": "quitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "regalo",
    "back": "present",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "present",
    "back": "regalo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "regresar",
    "back": "to return",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to return",
    "back": "regresar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "reír",
    "back": "to laugh",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to laugh",
    "back": "reír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "clothes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "clothes",
    "back": "ropa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "rubio",
    "back": "blonde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "blonde",
    "back": "rubio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "sábado",
    "back": "saturday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "saturday",
    "back": "sábado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "sala",
    "back": "living room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "living room",
    "back": "sala",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "salir",
    "back": "to go out",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to go out",
    "back": "salir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "secar",
    "back": "to dry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to dry",
    "back": "secar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "segundo",
    "back": "second",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "second",
    "back": "segundo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "seis",
    "back": "six",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "six",
    "back": "seis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "serio",
    "back": "serious",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "serious",
    "back": "serio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "siete",
    "back": "seven",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "seven",
    "back": "siete",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "sobre",
    "back": "about",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "about",
    "back": "sobre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "sonreír",
    "back": "to smile",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to smile",
    "back": "sonreír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "suficiente",
    "back": "sufficient",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "sufficient",
    "back": "suficiente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "supermercado",
    "back": "supermarket",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "supermarket",
    "back": "supermercado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "también",
    "back": "too/also",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "too/also",
    "back": "también",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tarde",
    "back": "afternoon",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "afternoon",
    "back": "tarde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "té",
    "back": "tea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "tea",
    "back": "té",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tecnología",
    "back": "technology",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "technology",
    "back": "tecnología",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "televisión",
    "back": "television",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "television",
    "back": "televisión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "temporada",
    "back": "season",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "season",
    "back": "temporada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tener",
    "back": "to have",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to have",
    "back": "tener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "terminar",
    "back": "to finish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to finish",
    "back": "terminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "terrible",
    "back": "terrible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "terrible",
    "back": "terrible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tiempo",
    "back": "time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "time",
    "back": "tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tipo",
    "back": "type",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "type",
    "back": "tipo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tocar",
    "back": "to play",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to play",
    "back": "tocar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "todavía",
    "back": "still",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "still",
    "back": "todavía",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "todo",
    "back": "all",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "all",
    "back": "todo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tomar",
    "back": "take",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "take",
    "back": "tomar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tostada",
    "back": "toast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "toast",
    "back": "tostada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajar",
    "back": "to work",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to work",
    "back": "trabajar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajo",
    "back": "work",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "work",
    "back": "trabajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tráfico",
    "back": "traffic",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "traffic",
    "back": "tráfico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "triste",
    "back": "sad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "triste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "tuyo",
    "back": "yours",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "yours",
    "back": "tuyo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "un par",
    "back": "a pair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "a pair",
    "back": "un par",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "vale",
    "back": "ok",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "ok",
    "back": "vale",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "veinte",
    "back": "twenty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "twenty",
    "back": "veinte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "ver",
    "back": "to see",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "ver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "viaje",
    "back": "journey",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "journey",
    "back": "viaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "vino",
    "back": "wine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "wine",
    "back": "vino",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "visitar",
    "back": "to visit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to visit",
    "back": "visitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "vivir",
    "back": "to live",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "vivir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "voleibol",
    "back": "volleyball",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "volleyball",
    "back": "voleibol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "volver",
    "back": "to return",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "to return",
    "back": "volver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Recognition",
    "front": "zapato",
    "back": "shoe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer::Production",
    "front": "shoe",
    "back": "zapato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::2 - La Otra Mujer",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "abrazar",
    "back": "to hug",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to hug",
    "back": "abrazar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "abril",
    "back": "april",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "april",
    "back": "abril",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "abuelo",
    "back": "grandfather",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "grandfather",
    "back": "abuelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "abrir",
    "back": "to open",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to open",
    "back": "abrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "adoptado",
    "back": "adopted",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "adopted",
    "back": "adoptado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ahora",
    "back": "now",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "now",
    "back": "ahora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "alto",
    "back": "tall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "tall",
    "back": "alto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "amable",
    "back": "friendly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "friendly",
    "back": "amable",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "amar",
    "back": "to love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to love",
    "back": "amar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ambos",
    "back": "both",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "both",
    "back": "ambos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "amigo",
    "back": "friend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "friend",
    "back": "amigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "amor",
    "back": "love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "love",
    "back": "amor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "año",
    "back": "year",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "year",
    "back": "año",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "aquí",
    "back": "here",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "here",
    "back": "aquí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ayudar",
    "back": "to help",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to help",
    "back": "ayudar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "azul",
    "back": "blue",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "blue",
    "back": "azul",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "a veces",
    "back": "sometimes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "sometimes",
    "back": "a veces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "beber",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "beber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "bebida",
    "back": "beverage",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "beverage",
    "back": "bebida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "besar",
    "back": "to kiss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to kiss",
    "back": "besar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "bicicleta",
    "back": "bike",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "bike",
    "back": "bicicleta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "bolsa",
    "back": "bag",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "bag",
    "back": "bolsa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "bonito",
    "back": "pretty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "pretty",
    "back": "bonito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "buen",
    "back": "good",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "good",
    "back": "buen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cada",
    "back": "each",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "each",
    "back": "cada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "café",
    "back": "coffee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "coffee",
    "back": "café",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "calor",
    "back": "heat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "heat",
    "back": "calor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "caminar",
    "back": "to walk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to walk",
    "back": "caminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cantar",
    "back": "to sing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to sing",
    "back": "cantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cara",
    "back": "face",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "face",
    "back": "cara",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "casa",
    "back": "house",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "house",
    "back": "casa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "centro commercial",
    "back": "shopping centre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "shopping centre",
    "back": "centro commercial",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cerveza",
    "back": "beer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "beer",
    "back": "cerveza",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "chico",
    "back": "boy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "boy",
    "back": "chico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cincuenta",
    "back": "fifty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "fifty",
    "back": "cincuenta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cine",
    "back": "cinema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "cinema",
    "back": "cine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ciudad",
    "back": "city",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "city",
    "back": "ciudad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "claro que sí",
    "back": "of course",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "of course",
    "back": "claro que sí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cocina",
    "back": "kitchen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "kitchen",
    "back": "cocina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "coincidencia",
    "back": "coincidence",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "coincidence",
    "back": "coincidencia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "comer",
    "back": "to eat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to eat",
    "back": "comer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "comida",
    "back": "food",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "food",
    "back": "comida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "como",
    "back": "like/how",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "like/how",
    "back": "como",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "comprar",
    "back": "to buy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to buy",
    "back": "comprar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "con",
    "back": "with",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "with",
    "back": "con",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "consejo",
    "back": "advice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "advice",
    "back": "consejo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cosa",
    "back": "thing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "thing",
    "back": "cosa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cuál",
    "back": "which",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "which",
    "back": "cuál",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cuando",
    "back": "when",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "when",
    "back": "cuando",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "cumpleaños",
    "back": "birthday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "birthday",
    "back": "cumpleaños",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "of",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "of",
    "back": "de",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "de nuevo",
    "back": "again",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "again",
    "back": "de nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "de repente",
    "back": "suddenly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "suddenly",
    "back": "de repente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "decir",
    "back": "to say",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to say",
    "back": "decir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "demasiado",
    "back": "too",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "too",
    "back": "demasiado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "desayunar",
    "back": "to eat breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to eat breakfast",
    "back": "desayunar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "descubrir",
    "back": "discover",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "discover",
    "back": "descubrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "desear",
    "back": "to wish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to wish",
    "back": "desear",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "deseo",
    "back": "a wish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "a wish",
    "back": "deseo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "después",
    "back": "after",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "after",
    "back": "después",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "día",
    "back": "day",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "day",
    "back": "día",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "diferencia",
    "back": "difference",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "difference",
    "back": "diferencia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "diferente",
    "back": "different",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "different",
    "back": "diferente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "difícil",
    "back": "difficult",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "difficult",
    "back": "difícil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "divertido",
    "back": "fun/funny",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "fun/funny",
    "back": "divertido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "dos",
    "back": "two",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "two",
    "back": "dos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ducharse",
    "back": "to shower",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to shower",
    "back": "ducharse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "enamorar",
    "back": "to fall in love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to fall in love",
    "back": "enamorar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "encantar",
    "back": "to love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to love",
    "back": "encantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "encontrar",
    "back": "to find",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to find",
    "back": "encontrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "enfrente",
    "back": "in front",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "in front",
    "back": "enfrente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "enorme",
    "back": "enormous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "enormous",
    "back": "enorme",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "entonces",
    "back": "then",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "then",
    "back": "entonces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "entrar",
    "back": "to enter",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to enter",
    "back": "entrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "escuela",
    "back": "school",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "school",
    "back": "escuela",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "eso",
    "back": "that",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "that",
    "back": "eso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "español",
    "back": "Spanish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "Spanish",
    "back": "español",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "especialmente",
    "back": "especially",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "especially",
    "back": "especialmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "esperar",
    "back": "to wait",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to wait",
    "back": "esperar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "estación",
    "back": "season",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "season",
    "back": "estación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "estar",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "estar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "expresión",
    "back": "expression",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "expression",
    "back": "expresión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "familia",
    "back": "family",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "family",
    "back": "familia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "favorito",
    "back": "favourite",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "favourite",
    "back": "favorito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "happy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "feliz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "fiesta",
    "back": "party",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "party",
    "back": "fiesta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "foto",
    "back": "photo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "photo",
    "back": "foto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "garaje",
    "back": "garage",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "garage",
    "back": "garaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "genial",
    "back": "great",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "great",
    "back": "genial",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "gracias",
    "back": "thank you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "thank you",
    "back": "gracias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "grande",
    "back": "big",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "big",
    "back": "grande",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "gritar",
    "back": "to shout",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to shout",
    "back": "gritar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "grupo",
    "back": "group",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "group",
    "back": "grupo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "gustar",
    "back": "to like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to like",
    "back": "gustar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hablar",
    "back": "to speak",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to speak",
    "back": "hablar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hace",
    "back": "ago",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "ago",
    "back": "hace",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hacer",
    "back": "to do/make",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to do/make",
    "back": "hacer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hasta",
    "back": "until",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "until",
    "back": "hasta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hay",
    "back": "there is",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "there is",
    "back": "hay",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hermano",
    "back": "brother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "brother",
    "back": "hermano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hermana",
    "back": "sister",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "sister",
    "back": "hermana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hijo",
    "back": "son/child",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "son/child",
    "back": "hijo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hola",
    "back": "hello",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "hello",
    "back": "hola",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hombre",
    "back": "man",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "man",
    "back": "hombre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hora",
    "back": "time/hour",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "time/hour",
    "back": "hora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hoy",
    "back": "today",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "today",
    "back": "hoy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "hoyuelos",
    "back": "dimples",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "dimples",
    "back": "hoyuelos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "huevo",
    "back": "egg",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "egg",
    "back": "huevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "imposible",
    "back": "impossible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "impossible",
    "back": "imposible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "increíble",
    "back": "incredible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "incredible",
    "back": "increíble",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ingeniero",
    "back": "engineer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "engineer",
    "back": "ingeniero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ir",
    "back": "to go",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to go",
    "back": "ir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "italia",
    "back": "Italy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "Italy",
    "back": "italia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "jueves",
    "back": "Thursday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "Thursday",
    "back": "jueves",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "junto",
    "back": "together",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "together",
    "back": "junto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "libre",
    "back": "free",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "free",
    "back": "libre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "llamar",
    "back": "to call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to call",
    "back": "llamar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "llegar",
    "back": "to arrive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to arrive",
    "back": "llegar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "llorar",
    "back": "to cry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to cry",
    "back": "llorar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "lloviendo",
    "back": "raining",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "raining",
    "back": "lloviendo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "levantar",
    "back": "to get up",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to get up",
    "back": "levantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "listo",
    "back": "ready",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "ready",
    "back": "listo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "lo siento",
    "back": "I’m sorry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "I’m sorry",
    "back": "lo siento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "madre",
    "back": "mother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "mother",
    "back": "madre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mañana",
    "back": "tomorrow",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "tomorrow",
    "back": "mañana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "marrón",
    "back": "brown",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "brown",
    "back": "marrón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "más",
    "back": "more",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "more",
    "back": "más",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "matemáticas",
    "back": "maths",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "maths",
    "back": "matemáticas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mayor",
    "back": "older",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "older",
    "back": "mayor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mejor",
    "back": "best",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "best",
    "back": "mejor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mentira",
    "back": "lie",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "lie",
    "back": "mentira",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mientras",
    "back": "while",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "while",
    "back": "mientras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "minuto",
    "back": "minute",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "minute",
    "back": "minuto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mirar",
    "back": "to watch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to watch",
    "back": "mirar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mismo",
    "back": "same",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "same",
    "back": "mismo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "montar",
    "back": "to ride",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to ride",
    "back": "montar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "moto",
    "back": "motorbike",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "motorbike",
    "back": "moto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho",
    "back": "many",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "many",
    "back": "mucho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mujer",
    "back": "woman",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "woman",
    "back": "mujer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "mundo",
    "back": "world",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "world",
    "back": "mundo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "música",
    "back": "music",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "music",
    "back": "música",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "muy",
    "back": "very",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "very",
    "back": "muy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "nada",
    "back": "nothing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "nothing",
    "back": "nada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "naranja",
    "back": "orange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "orange",
    "back": "naranja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "nariz",
    "back": "nose",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "nose",
    "back": "nariz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "necesitar",
    "back": "to need",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to need",
    "back": "necesitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "negro",
    "back": "black",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "black",
    "back": "negro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "nombre",
    "back": "name",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "name",
    "back": "nombre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "novio",
    "back": "boyfriend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "boyfriend",
    "back": "novio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "nueve",
    "back": "nine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "nine",
    "back": "nueve",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "nuevo",
    "back": "new",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "new",
    "back": "nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ojo",
    "back": "eye",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "eye",
    "back": "ojo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "opción",
    "back": "option",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "option",
    "back": "opción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "orfanato",
    "back": "orphanage",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "orphanage",
    "back": "orfanato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "otro",
    "back": "other",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "other",
    "back": "otro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "padre",
    "back": "dad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "dad",
    "back": "padre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "para",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "para",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pasar",
    "back": "to spend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to spend",
    "back": "pasar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pasatiempo",
    "back": "hobby",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "hobby",
    "back": "pasatiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pastel",
    "back": "cake",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "cake",
    "back": "pastel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pausa",
    "back": "pause",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "pause",
    "back": "pausa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "película",
    "back": "film",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "film",
    "back": "película",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pelo",
    "back": "hair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "hair",
    "back": "pelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "parecer",
    "back": "to seem like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to seem like",
    "back": "parecer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pensar",
    "back": "to think",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to think",
    "back": "pensar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "perfecto",
    "back": "perfect",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "perfect",
    "back": "perfecto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pero",
    "back": "but",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "but",
    "back": "pero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "piscina",
    "back": "swimming pool",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "swimming pool",
    "back": "piscina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "pista de tenis",
    "back": "tennis court",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "tennis court",
    "back": "pista de tenis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "plátano",
    "back": "banana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "banana",
    "back": "plátano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "popular",
    "back": "popular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "popular",
    "back": "popular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "porque",
    "back": "because",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "because",
    "back": "porque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "por",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "por",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "posible",
    "back": "possible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "possible",
    "back": "posible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "primavera",
    "back": "spring",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "spring",
    "back": "primavera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "primero",
    "back": "first",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "first",
    "back": "primero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "próximo",
    "back": "next",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "next",
    "back": "próximo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "poder",
    "back": "to be able to",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to be able to",
    "back": "poder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ponerse",
    "back": "to put on",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to put on",
    "back": "ponerse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "por ejemplo",
    "back": "for example",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "for example",
    "back": "por ejemplo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "por favor",
    "back": "please",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "please",
    "back": "por favor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "preguntar",
    "back": "to ask",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to ask",
    "back": "preguntar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "problema",
    "back": "problem",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "problem",
    "back": "problema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "puerta",
    "back": "door",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "door",
    "back": "puerta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "rizado",
    "back": "curly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "curly",
    "back": "rizado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "qué tal",
    "back": "how are you?",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "how are you?",
    "back": "qué tal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "querer",
    "back": "to want",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to want",
    "back": "querer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "quién",
    "back": "who",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "who",
    "back": "quién",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "quizás",
    "back": "perhaps",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "perhaps",
    "back": "quizás",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "regalo",
    "back": "present",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "present",
    "back": "regalo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "reír",
    "back": "to laugh",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to laugh",
    "back": "reír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "reloj",
    "back": "watch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "watch",
    "back": "reloj",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "responder",
    "back": "to respond",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to respond",
    "back": "responder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "clothes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "clothes",
    "back": "ropa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "saber",
    "back": "to know",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to know",
    "back": "saber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "sala",
    "back": "living room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "living room",
    "back": "sala",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "salir",
    "back": "to go out",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to go out",
    "back": "salir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "secreto",
    "back": "secret",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "secret",
    "back": "secreto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "segundo",
    "back": "second",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "second",
    "back": "segundo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "seguro",
    "back": "sure",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "sure",
    "back": "seguro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "sentir",
    "back": "to feel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to feel",
    "back": "sentir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ser",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "ser",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "serio",
    "back": "serious",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "serious",
    "back": "serio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "sevilla",
    "back": "Seville",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "Seville",
    "back": "sevilla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "si",
    "back": "if",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "if",
    "back": "si",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "sí",
    "back": "yes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "yes",
    "back": "sí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "similar",
    "back": "similar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "similar",
    "back": "similar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "sobre",
    "back": "about",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "about",
    "back": "sobre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "soltero",
    "back": "single",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "single",
    "back": "soltero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "soplar",
    "back": "to blow",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to blow",
    "back": "soplar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "su",
    "back": "his/her",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "his/her",
    "back": "su",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "también",
    "back": "too",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "too",
    "back": "también",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tarde",
    "back": "afternoon",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "afternoon",
    "back": "tarde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "té",
    "back": "tea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "tea",
    "back": "té",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "teléfono",
    "back": "telephone",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "telephone",
    "back": "teléfono",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tener",
    "back": "to have",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to have",
    "back": "tener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tiempo",
    "back": "time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "time",
    "back": "tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tío",
    "back": "uncle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "uncle",
    "back": "tío",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tocar",
    "back": "to touch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to touch",
    "back": "tocar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "todos",
    "back": "all",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "all",
    "back": "todos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tomar",
    "back": "to take",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to take",
    "back": "tomar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tomate",
    "back": "tomato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "tomato",
    "back": "tomate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "tostada",
    "back": "toast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "toast",
    "back": "tostada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "total",
    "back": "total",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "total",
    "back": "total",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajar",
    "back": "to work",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to work",
    "back": "trabajar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajo",
    "back": "job",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "job",
    "back": "trabajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "treinta y cinco",
    "back": "thirty five",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "thirty five",
    "back": "treinta y cinco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "triste",
    "back": "sad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "triste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "vale",
    "back": "ok",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "ok",
    "back": "vale",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "veintidos",
    "back": "twenty two",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "twenty two",
    "back": "veintidos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "veintinueve",
    "back": "twenty nine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "twenty nine",
    "back": "veintinueve",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "veintiseis",
    "back": "twenty six",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "twenty six",
    "back": "veintiseis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "vela",
    "back": "candle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "candle",
    "back": "vela",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "ver",
    "back": "to see",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "ver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "vino",
    "back": "wine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "wine",
    "back": "vino",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "visitar",
    "back": "to visit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to visit",
    "back": "visitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "vivir",
    "back": "to live",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "vivir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "volver",
    "back": "to return",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "to return",
    "back": "volver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "y",
    "back": "and",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "and",
    "back": "y",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Recognition",
    "front": "zumo",
    "back": "juice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?::Production",
    "front": "juice",
    "back": "zumo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::3 - ¿Quién Es Mi Padre?",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "abrigo",
    "back": "coat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "coat",
    "back": "abrigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "abrir",
    "back": "to open",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to open",
    "back": "abrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "absurdo",
    "back": "absurd",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "absurd",
    "back": "absurdo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "actor",
    "back": "actor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "actor",
    "back": "actor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "actriz",
    "back": "actress",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "actress",
    "back": "actriz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "a veces",
    "back": "sometimes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sometimes",
    "back": "a veces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "afortunado",
    "back": "fortunate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "fortunate",
    "back": "afortunado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ahora",
    "back": "now",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "now",
    "back": "ahora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "al menos",
    "back": "at least",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "at least",
    "back": "al menos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "alto",
    "back": "high/tall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "high/tall",
    "back": "alto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "allí",
    "back": "there",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "there",
    "back": "allí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "amar",
    "back": "to love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to love",
    "back": "amar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "amigo",
    "back": "friend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "friend",
    "back": "amigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "año",
    "back": "year",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "year",
    "back": "año",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "apartamento",
    "back": "apartment",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "apartment",
    "back": "apartamento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "aplicar",
    "back": "to apply",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to apply",
    "back": "aplicar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "aquí",
    "back": "here",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "here",
    "back": "aquí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "atractivo",
    "back": "attractive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "attractive",
    "back": "atractivo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "autor",
    "back": "author",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "author",
    "back": "autor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ayudar",
    "back": "to help",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to help",
    "back": "ayudar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "azul",
    "back": "blue",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "blue",
    "back": "azul",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "baño",
    "back": "bathroom",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "bathroom",
    "back": "baño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "barato",
    "back": "cheap",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "cheap",
    "back": "barato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "bebida",
    "back": "drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "drink",
    "back": "bebida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "beber",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "beber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "bien",
    "back": "well",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "well",
    "back": "bien",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "blanco",
    "back": "white",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "white",
    "back": "blanco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "bolsa",
    "back": "bag",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "bag",
    "back": "bolsa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "bonito",
    "back": "beautiful",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "beautiful",
    "back": "bonito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "botón",
    "back": "button",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "button",
    "back": "botón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "buen humor",
    "back": "good mood",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "good mood",
    "back": "buen humor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cada",
    "back": "each",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "each",
    "back": "cada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "café",
    "back": "coffee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "coffee",
    "back": "café",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cámara",
    "back": "camera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "camera",
    "back": "cámara",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cambiar",
    "back": "to change",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to change",
    "back": "cambiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "caminar",
    "back": "to walk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to walk",
    "back": "caminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "campo",
    "back": "countryside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "countryside",
    "back": "campo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cantar",
    "back": "to sing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to sing",
    "back": "cantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "caro",
    "back": "expensive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "expensive",
    "back": "caro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "casa",
    "back": "house",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "house",
    "back": "casa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "celoso",
    "back": "jealous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "jealous",
    "back": "celoso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cenar",
    "back": "to have dinner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to have dinner",
    "back": "cenar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cepillar",
    "back": "to brush",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to brush",
    "back": "cepillar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cerrar",
    "back": "to close",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to close",
    "back": "cerrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "chica",
    "back": "girl",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "girl",
    "back": "chica",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "chico",
    "back": "boy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "boy",
    "back": "chico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "chiste",
    "back": "joke",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "joke",
    "back": "chiste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cita",
    "back": "date",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "date",
    "back": "cita",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ciudad",
    "back": "city",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "city",
    "back": "ciudad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "coche",
    "back": "car",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "car",
    "back": "coche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cocina",
    "back": "kitchen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "kitchen",
    "back": "cocina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "comida",
    "back": "food",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "food",
    "back": "comida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cómodo",
    "back": "comfortable",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "comfortable",
    "back": "cómodo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "compañeros",
    "back": "collagues",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "collagues",
    "back": "compañeros",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "compromiso",
    "back": "commitment",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "commitment",
    "back": "compromiso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "comunidad",
    "back": "community",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "community",
    "back": "comunidad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "con",
    "back": "with",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "with",
    "back": "con",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "conducir",
    "back": "to drive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to drive",
    "back": "conducir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "conmigo",
    "back": "with me",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "with me",
    "back": "conmigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "contactar",
    "back": "to contact",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to contact",
    "back": "contactar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "contacto",
    "back": "contact",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "contact",
    "back": "contacto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "contar",
    "back": "to tell",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to tell",
    "back": "contar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "controlar",
    "back": "to control",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to control",
    "back": "controlar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "correr",
    "back": "to run",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to run",
    "back": "correr",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cosa",
    "back": "thing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "thing",
    "back": "cosa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "creer",
    "back": "to believe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to believe",
    "back": "creer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "crítica",
    "back": "critical",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "critical",
    "back": "crítica",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cuando",
    "back": "when",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "when",
    "back": "cuando",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "cuatro",
    "back": "four",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "four",
    "back": "cuatro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "culpa",
    "back": "fault",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "fault",
    "back": "culpa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "of",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "of",
    "back": "de",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "de repente",
    "back": "suddenly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "suddenly",
    "back": "de repente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "decir",
    "back": "to say",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to say",
    "back": "decir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "delante",
    "back": "in front",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "in front",
    "back": "delante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "delgado",
    "back": "slim",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "slim",
    "back": "delgado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "demasiado",
    "back": "too",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "too",
    "back": "demasiado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "departamento",
    "back": "department",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "department",
    "back": "departamento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "deporte",
    "back": "sport",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sport",
    "back": "deporte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "desayuno",
    "back": "breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "breakfast",
    "back": "desayuno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "descansar",
    "back": "to rest",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to rest",
    "back": "descansar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "después",
    "back": "after",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "after",
    "back": "después",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "día",
    "back": "day",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "day",
    "back": "día",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "dientes",
    "back": "teeth",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "teeth",
    "back": "dientes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "diez",
    "back": "ten",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "ten",
    "back": "diez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "diferente",
    "back": "different",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "different",
    "back": "diferente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "difícil",
    "back": "difficult",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "difficult",
    "back": "difícil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "divertido",
    "back": "fun",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "fun",
    "back": "divertido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "domingo",
    "back": "Sunday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "Sunday",
    "back": "domingo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "dos",
    "back": "two",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "two",
    "back": "dos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ducharse",
    "back": "to shower",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to shower",
    "back": "ducharse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "duda",
    "back": "doubt",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "doubt",
    "back": "duda",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "edificio",
    "back": "building",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "building",
    "back": "edificio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "elección",
    "back": "choice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "choice",
    "back": "elección",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "empezar",
    "back": "to start",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to start",
    "back": "empezar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "en",
    "back": "in",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "in",
    "back": "en",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "en serio",
    "back": "seriously",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "seriously",
    "back": "en serio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "en frente",
    "back": "infront",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "infront",
    "back": "en frente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "encantar",
    "back": "to love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to love",
    "back": "encantar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "enfadado",
    "back": "annoyed",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "annoyed",
    "back": "enfadado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "entender",
    "back": "to understand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to understand",
    "back": "entender",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "entrar",
    "back": "to enter",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to enter",
    "back": "entrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "escalera",
    "back": "stairs",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "stairs",
    "back": "escalera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "escritor",
    "back": "writer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "writer",
    "back": "escritor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "escuchar",
    "back": "to listen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to listen",
    "back": "escuchar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "eso",
    "back": "that",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "that",
    "back": "eso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "espacio",
    "back": "space",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "space",
    "back": "espacio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "esperar",
    "back": "to wait",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to wait",
    "back": "esperar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "estavez",
    "back": "this time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "this time",
    "back": "estavez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "estar",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "estar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "exactamente",
    "back": "exactly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "exactly",
    "back": "exactamente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "excelente",
    "back": "excellent",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "excellent",
    "back": "excelente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "exclusivo",
    "back": "exclusive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "exclusive",
    "back": "exclusivo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "exterior",
    "back": "exterior",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "exterior",
    "back": "exterior",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "fácil",
    "back": "easy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "easy",
    "back": "fácil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "famoso",
    "back": "famous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "famous",
    "back": "famoso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "happy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "feliz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "físico",
    "back": "physical",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "physical",
    "back": "físico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "fondo croma",
    "back": "green screen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "green screen",
    "back": "fondo croma",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "francés",
    "back": "French",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "French",
    "back": "francés",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "frenéticamente",
    "back": "frantically",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "frantically",
    "back": "frenéticamente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "frío",
    "back": "cold",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "cold",
    "back": "frío",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "funcionar",
    "back": "to function",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to function",
    "back": "funcionar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "fútbol",
    "back": "football",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "football",
    "back": "fútbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "gobierno",
    "back": "government",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "government",
    "back": "gobierno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "gracias",
    "back": "thank you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "thank you",
    "back": "gracias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "grand",
    "back": "big",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "big",
    "back": "grand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "gratis",
    "back": "free",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "free",
    "back": "gratis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "gritar",
    "back": "to shout",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to shout",
    "back": "gritar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "guapo",
    "back": "handsome",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "handsome",
    "back": "guapo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "guiñar",
    "back": "to wink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to wink",
    "back": "guiñar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "gustar",
    "back": "to like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to like",
    "back": "gustar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "habitación",
    "back": "bedoom",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "bedoom",
    "back": "habitación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hablar",
    "back": "to speak",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to speak",
    "back": "hablar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hace",
    "back": "ago",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "ago",
    "back": "hace",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hacer",
    "back": "to do",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to do",
    "back": "hacer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hacia",
    "back": "toward",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "toward",
    "back": "hacia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hambre",
    "back": "hunger",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "hunger",
    "back": "hambre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hasta luego",
    "back": "see you later",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "see you later",
    "back": "hasta luego",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hay",
    "back": "there is",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "there is",
    "back": "hay",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hielo",
    "back": "ice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "ice",
    "back": "hielo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hola",
    "back": "hello",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "hello",
    "back": "hola",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hombre",
    "back": "man",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "man",
    "back": "hombre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hombre del tiempo",
    "back": "weatherman",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "weatherman",
    "back": "hombre del tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hora",
    "back": "hour",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "hour",
    "back": "hora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "hoy",
    "back": "today",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "today",
    "back": "hoy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "huracán",
    "back": "hurricane",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "hurricane",
    "back": "huracán",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "igualmente",
    "back": "equally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "equally",
    "back": "igualmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "importante",
    "back": "important",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "important",
    "back": "importante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "increíble",
    "back": "incredible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "incredible",
    "back": "increíble",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "informe",
    "back": "report",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "report",
    "back": "informe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "intentar",
    "back": "to try",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to try",
    "back": "intentar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ir",
    "back": "to go",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to go",
    "back": "ir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "jefa",
    "back": "boss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "boss",
    "back": "jefa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "jugadoras",
    "back": "players",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "players",
    "back": "jugadoras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "junto",
    "back": "together",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "together",
    "back": "junto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "leer",
    "back": "to read",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to read",
    "back": "leer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "levantarse",
    "back": "to get up",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to get up",
    "back": "levantarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llamada",
    "back": "call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "call",
    "back": "llamada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llamar",
    "back": "to call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to call",
    "back": "llamar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llave",
    "back": "key",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "key",
    "back": "llave",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llegar",
    "back": "to arrive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to arrive",
    "back": "llegar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llevar",
    "back": "to wear",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to wear",
    "back": "llevar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "llevar bien",
    "back": "get along",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "get along",
    "back": "llevar bien",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "libertad",
    "back": "freedom",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "freedom",
    "back": "libertad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "listo",
    "back": "ready",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "ready",
    "back": "listo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "lo siento",
    "back": "sorry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sorry",
    "back": "lo siento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "loco",
    "back": "crazy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "crazy",
    "back": "loco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "lunes",
    "back": "Monday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "Monday",
    "back": "lunes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "madre",
    "back": "mother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "mother",
    "back": "madre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mañana",
    "back": "tomorrow",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "tomorrow",
    "back": "mañana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "maquilladora",
    "back": "makeup artist",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "makeup artist",
    "back": "maquilladora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "maquillaje",
    "back": "makeup",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "makeup",
    "back": "maquillaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "marca",
    "back": "brand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "brand",
    "back": "marca",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "marrón",
    "back": "brown",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "brown",
    "back": "marrón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "más",
    "back": "more",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "more",
    "back": "más",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mejor",
    "back": "best",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "best",
    "back": "mejor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "menos",
    "back": "less",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "less",
    "back": "menos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mientras",
    "back": "while",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "while",
    "back": "mientras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "miercoles",
    "back": "Wednesday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "Wednesday",
    "back": "miercoles",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "minuto",
    "back": "minute",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "minute",
    "back": "minuto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mirar",
    "back": "to look",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to look",
    "back": "mirar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mismo",
    "back": "same",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "same",
    "back": "mismo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "molestar",
    "back": "to bother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to bother",
    "back": "molestar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mono",
    "back": "cute",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "cute",
    "back": "mono",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "morir",
    "back": "to die",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to die",
    "back": "morir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "moto",
    "back": "motorbike",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "motorbike",
    "back": "moto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "móvil",
    "back": "mobile",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "mobile",
    "back": "móvil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "movimiento",
    "back": "movement",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "movement",
    "back": "movimiento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho",
    "back": "many",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "many",
    "back": "mucho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho gusto",
    "back": "nice to meet you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "nice to meet you",
    "back": "mucho gusto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mujer",
    "back": "woman",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "woman",
    "back": "mujer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "mundo",
    "back": "world",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "world",
    "back": "mundo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "música",
    "back": "music",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "music",
    "back": "música",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "muy",
    "back": "very",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "very",
    "back": "muy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nada",
    "back": "nothing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "nothing",
    "back": "nada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nadie",
    "back": "nobody",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "nobody",
    "back": "nadie",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "natural",
    "back": "natural",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "natural",
    "back": "natural",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "necesitar",
    "back": "to need",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to need",
    "back": "necesitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "negro",
    "back": "black",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "black",
    "back": "negro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nervioso",
    "back": "nervous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "nervous",
    "back": "nervioso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ninguna",
    "back": "any",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "any",
    "back": "ninguna",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "no",
    "back": "no/not",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "no/not",
    "back": "no",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "noche",
    "back": "night",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "night",
    "back": "noche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nosotros",
    "back": "us",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "us",
    "back": "nosotros",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "noticias",
    "back": "news",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "news",
    "back": "noticias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "novia",
    "back": "girlfriend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "girlfriend",
    "back": "novia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "novio",
    "back": "boyfriend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "boyfriend",
    "back": "novio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nuestro",
    "back": "our",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "our",
    "back": "nuestro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "nuevo",
    "back": "new",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "new",
    "back": "nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "obtener",
    "back": "to get",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to get",
    "back": "obtener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "oficina",
    "back": "office",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "office",
    "back": "oficina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ojo",
    "back": "eye",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "eye",
    "back": "ojo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "opción",
    "back": "option",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "option",
    "back": "opción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "opinión",
    "back": "opinion",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "opinion",
    "back": "opinión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "orgulloso",
    "back": "proud",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "proud",
    "back": "orgulloso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "otro",
    "back": "other",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "other",
    "back": "otro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "padre",
    "back": "father",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "father",
    "back": "padre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "país",
    "back": "country",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "country",
    "back": "país",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "palabra",
    "back": "word",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "word",
    "back": "palabra",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pálido",
    "back": "pale",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "pale",
    "back": "pálido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pantalla",
    "back": "screen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "screen",
    "back": "pantalla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "para",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "para",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "parecer",
    "back": "to seem",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to seem",
    "back": "parecer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pared",
    "back": "wall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "wall",
    "back": "pared",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pareja",
    "back": "couple",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "couple",
    "back": "pareja",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pasar",
    "back": "to spend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to spend",
    "back": "pasar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pasillo",
    "back": "corridor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "corridor",
    "back": "pasillo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "peligroso",
    "back": "dangerous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "dangerous",
    "back": "peligroso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pelo",
    "back": "hair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "hair",
    "back": "pelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pensamientos",
    "back": "thoughts",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "thoughts",
    "back": "pensamientos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pensar",
    "back": "to think",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to think",
    "back": "pensar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pequeño",
    "back": "small",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "small",
    "back": "pequeño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "perfecto",
    "back": "perfect",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "perfect",
    "back": "perfecto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "periódico",
    "back": "newspaper",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "newspaper",
    "back": "periódico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pero",
    "back": "but",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "but",
    "back": "pero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "persona",
    "back": "person",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "person",
    "back": "persona",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "pie",
    "back": "foot",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "foot",
    "back": "pie",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "piel",
    "back": "skin",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "skin",
    "back": "piel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "piso",
    "back": "floor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "floor",
    "back": "piso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "plátano",
    "back": "banana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "banana",
    "back": "plátano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "poder",
    "back": "to be able to",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to be able to",
    "back": "poder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "(el) poder",
    "back": "the power",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "the power",
    "back": "(el) poder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "policía",
    "back": "police",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "police",
    "back": "policía",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ponerse",
    "back": "to put on",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to put on",
    "back": "ponerse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "popular",
    "back": "popular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "popular",
    "back": "popular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "por",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "por",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "por ejemplo",
    "back": "for example",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "for example",
    "back": "por ejemplo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "por favor",
    "back": "please",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "please",
    "back": "por favor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "por fin",
    "back": "finally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "finally",
    "back": "por fin",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "por lo menos",
    "back": "at least",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "at least",
    "back": "por lo menos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "porque",
    "back": "because",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "because",
    "back": "porque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "preguntar",
    "back": "to ask",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to ask",
    "back": "preguntar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "preocupado",
    "back": "worried",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "worried",
    "back": "preocupado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "preparar",
    "back": "to prepare",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to prepare",
    "back": "preparar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "preocuparse",
    "back": "to worry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to worry",
    "back": "preocuparse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "presentadores",
    "back": "presenters",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "presenters",
    "back": "presentadores",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "primero",
    "back": "first",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "first",
    "back": "primero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "probar",
    "back": "to try",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to try",
    "back": "probar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "problema",
    "back": "problem",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "problem",
    "back": "problema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "prueba",
    "back": "test",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "test",
    "back": "prueba",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "puerta",
    "back": "door",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "door",
    "back": "puerta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "querer",
    "back": "to want",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to want",
    "back": "querer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "quince",
    "back": "fifteen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "fifteen",
    "back": "quince",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "quizás",
    "back": "perhaps",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "perhaps",
    "back": "quizás",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "raro",
    "back": "strange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "strange",
    "back": "raro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "realmente",
    "back": "really",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "really",
    "back": "realmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "regular",
    "back": "regular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "regular",
    "back": "regular",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "reír",
    "back": "to laugh",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to laugh",
    "back": "reír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "relación",
    "back": "relationship",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "relationship",
    "back": "relación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "reloj",
    "back": "watch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "watch",
    "back": "reloj",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "repetir",
    "back": "to repeat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to repeat",
    "back": "repetir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "reportar",
    "back": "to report",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to report",
    "back": "reportar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "respetuoso",
    "back": "respectful",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "respectful",
    "back": "respetuoso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "responder",
    "back": "to respond",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to respond",
    "back": "responder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "respuesta",
    "back": "reponse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "reponse",
    "back": "respuesta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "restaurantes",
    "back": "restaurant",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "restaurant",
    "back": "restaurantes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "clothes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "clothes",
    "back": "ropa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "saber",
    "back": "to know",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to know",
    "back": "saber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sala",
    "back": "living room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "living room",
    "back": "sala",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "salir",
    "back": "to go out",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to go out",
    "back": "salir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "secreto",
    "back": "secret",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "secret",
    "back": "secreto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sensible",
    "back": "sensitive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sensitive",
    "back": "sensible",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sentarse",
    "back": "to sit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to sit",
    "back": "sentarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ser",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "ser",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "si",
    "back": "if",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "if",
    "back": "si",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sí",
    "back": "yes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "yes",
    "back": "sí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "siempre",
    "back": "always",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "always",
    "back": "siempre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "siguiente",
    "back": "following",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "following",
    "back": "siguiente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "silencio",
    "back": "silence",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "silence",
    "back": "silencio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "silla",
    "back": "seat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "seat",
    "back": "silla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sobre",
    "back": "over",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "over",
    "back": "sobre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sofa",
    "back": "sofa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sofa",
    "back": "sofa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sol",
    "back": "sun",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sun",
    "back": "sol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "solo",
    "back": "alone",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "alone",
    "back": "solo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sonreír",
    "back": "to smile",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to smile",
    "back": "sonreír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sorprendido",
    "back": "surprised",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "surprised",
    "back": "sorprendido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "su",
    "back": "his/her",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "his/her",
    "back": "su",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "sueldo",
    "back": "salary",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "salary",
    "back": "sueldo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "suerte",
    "back": "lucky",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "lucky",
    "back": "suerte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "suficiente",
    "back": "sufficient",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sufficient",
    "back": "suficiente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "super",
    "back": "super",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "super",
    "back": "super",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "también",
    "back": "also",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "also",
    "back": "también",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tarde",
    "back": "late",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "late",
    "back": "tarde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "teléfono",
    "back": "telephone",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "telephone",
    "back": "teléfono",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "televisión",
    "back": "television",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "television",
    "back": "televisión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "temprano",
    "back": "early",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "early",
    "back": "temprano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tener",
    "back": "to have",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to have",
    "back": "tener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tiempo",
    "back": "weather",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "weather",
    "back": "tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tipo",
    "back": "type",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "type",
    "back": "tipo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "todo",
    "back": "all",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "all",
    "back": "todo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tomar",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "tomar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tornado",
    "back": "tornado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "tornado",
    "back": "tornado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajo",
    "back": "job",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "job",
    "back": "trabajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "traje",
    "back": "suit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "suit",
    "back": "traje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tres",
    "back": "three",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "three",
    "back": "tres",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "triste",
    "back": "sad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "triste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "tristemente",
    "back": "sadly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "sadly",
    "back": "tristemente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "último",
    "back": "final",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "final",
    "back": "último",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "única",
    "back": "only",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "only",
    "back": "única",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "usar",
    "back": "to use",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to use",
    "back": "usar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "útil",
    "back": "useful",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "useful",
    "back": "útil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vale",
    "back": "ok",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "ok",
    "back": "vale",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ventana",
    "back": "window",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "window",
    "back": "ventana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ventanilla",
    "back": "window (in a car)",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "window (in a car)",
    "back": "ventanilla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "ver",
    "back": "to see",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "ver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "verano",
    "back": "summer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "summer",
    "back": "verano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "verde",
    "back": "green",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "green",
    "back": "verde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vestido",
    "back": "dress",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "dress",
    "back": "vestido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vez",
    "back": "time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "time",
    "back": "vez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vida",
    "back": "life",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "life",
    "back": "vida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vino",
    "back": "wine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "wine",
    "back": "vino",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "visitar",
    "back": "to visit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to visit",
    "back": "visitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "vivir",
    "back": "to live",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "vivir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "y",
    "back": "and",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "and",
    "back": "y",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Recognition",
    "front": "zapatos",
    "back": "shoes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo::Production",
    "front": "shoes",
    "back": "zapatos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::4 - El Hombre Del Tiempo",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "a menudo",
    "back": "often",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "often",
    "back": "a menudo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "abrazar",
    "back": "to hug",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to hug",
    "back": "abrazar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "abrir",
    "back": "to open",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to open",
    "back": "abrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "aburrido",
    "back": "boring",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "boring",
    "back": "aburrido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "acampar",
    "back": "camping",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "camping",
    "back": "acampar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "actividad",
    "back": "activity",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "activity",
    "back": "actividad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "adios",
    "back": "goodbye",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "goodbye",
    "back": "adios",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "adolescente",
    "back": "teenager",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "teenager",
    "back": "adolescente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "afuera",
    "back": "outside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "outside",
    "back": "afuera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ahí",
    "back": "there",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "there",
    "back": "ahí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ahora",
    "back": "now",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "now",
    "back": "ahora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ahorrar",
    "back": "to save",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to save",
    "back": "ahorrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "aire libre",
    "back": "outdoors",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "outdoors",
    "back": "aire libre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "albañil",
    "back": "builder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "builder",
    "back": "albañil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "alcohol",
    "back": "alcohol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "alcohol",
    "back": "alcohol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "alguien",
    "back": "someone",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "someone",
    "back": "alguien",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "alivio",
    "back": "relief",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "relief",
    "back": "alivio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "almorzar",
    "back": "to have lunch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to have lunch",
    "back": "almorzar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "alto",
    "back": "tall/high",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "tall/high",
    "back": "alto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ambos",
    "back": "both",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "both",
    "back": "ambos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "amigo",
    "back": "friend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "friend",
    "back": "amigo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "amor",
    "back": "love",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "love",
    "back": "amor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "año",
    "back": "year",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "year",
    "back": "año",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "antes",
    "back": "before",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "before",
    "back": "antes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "antipático",
    "back": "nasty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "nasty",
    "back": "antipático",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "apartamento",
    "back": "apartment",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "apartment",
    "back": "apartamento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "aquí",
    "back": "here",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "here",
    "back": "aquí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "área de construcción",
    "back": "building site",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "building site",
    "back": "área de construcción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "armario",
    "back": "wardrobe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "wardrobe",
    "back": "armario",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "atlético",
    "back": "athletic",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "athletic",
    "back": "atlético",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ayudar",
    "back": "to help",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to help",
    "back": "ayudar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "baño",
    "back": "bathroom",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bathroom",
    "back": "baño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "barato",
    "back": "cheap",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cheap",
    "back": "barato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "barba",
    "back": "beard",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "beard",
    "back": "barba",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "barrio",
    "back": "neighbourhood",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "neighbourhood",
    "back": "barrio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bebé",
    "back": "baby",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "baby",
    "back": "bebé",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "beber",
    "back": "to drink",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to drink",
    "back": "beber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "beneficio",
    "back": "benefit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "benefit",
    "back": "beneficio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "besar",
    "back": "to kiss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to kiss",
    "back": "besar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bicicleta",
    "back": "bicycle",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bicycle",
    "back": "bicicleta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bien",
    "back": "well",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "well",
    "back": "bien",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "blanco",
    "back": "white",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "white",
    "back": "blanco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bocadillo",
    "back": "sandwich",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sandwich",
    "back": "bocadillo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bolso",
    "back": "bag",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bag",
    "back": "bolso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "brillar",
    "back": "to shine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to shine",
    "back": "brillar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "buena forma",
    "back": "good shape",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "good shape",
    "back": "buena forma",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "bueno",
    "back": "good",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "good",
    "back": "bueno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cabeza",
    "back": "head",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "head",
    "back": "cabeza",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cada",
    "back": "each",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "each",
    "back": "cada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "café",
    "back": "coffee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "coffee",
    "back": "café",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "calidad",
    "back": "quality",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "quality",
    "back": "calidad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cama",
    "back": "bed",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bed",
    "back": "cama",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cámara",
    "back": "camera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "camera",
    "back": "cámara",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cambiar",
    "back": "to change",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to change",
    "back": "cambiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "caminar",
    "back": "to walk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to walk",
    "back": "caminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "campo",
    "back": "countryside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "countryside",
    "back": "campo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cansado",
    "back": "tired",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "tired",
    "back": "cansado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cara",
    "back": "face",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "face",
    "back": "cara",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cárcel",
    "back": "prison",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "prison",
    "back": "cárcel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "casa",
    "back": "house",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "house",
    "back": "casa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "casi",
    "back": "almost",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "almost",
    "back": "casi",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "causa",
    "back": "cause",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cause",
    "back": "causa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "celebrar",
    "back": "to celebrate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to celebrate",
    "back": "celebrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cena",
    "back": "dinner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "dinner",
    "back": "cena",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cerca",
    "back": "near",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "near",
    "back": "cerca",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "chocolate",
    "back": "chocolate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "chocolate",
    "back": "chocolate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cinco",
    "back": "five",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "five",
    "back": "cinco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cigarillo",
    "back": "cigarette",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cigarette",
    "back": "cigarillo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cine",
    "back": "cinema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cinema",
    "back": "cine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "claro",
    "back": "sure",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sure",
    "back": "claro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cliente",
    "back": "client",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "client",
    "back": "cliente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cocina",
    "back": "kitchen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "kitchen",
    "back": "cocina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cocinar",
    "back": "to cook",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to cook",
    "back": "cocinar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "comedor",
    "back": "dining room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "dining room",
    "back": "comedor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "comentar",
    "back": "to comment",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to comment",
    "back": "comentar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "comer",
    "back": "to eat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to eat",
    "back": "comer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "como",
    "back": "like/as",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "like/as",
    "back": "como",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "comprar",
    "back": "to buy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to buy",
    "back": "comprar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "con",
    "back": "with",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "with",
    "back": "con",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "conducir",
    "back": "to drive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to drive",
    "back": "conducir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "construcción",
    "back": "construction",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "construction",
    "back": "construcción",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "construir",
    "back": "to build",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to build",
    "back": "construir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "contratar",
    "back": "to contract",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to contract",
    "back": "contratar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "corazón",
    "back": "heart",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "heart",
    "back": "corazón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "correr",
    "back": "to run",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to run",
    "back": "correr",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cosa",
    "back": "thing",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "thing",
    "back": "cosa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "costar",
    "back": "to cost",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to cost",
    "back": "costar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cuando",
    "back": "when",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "when",
    "back": "cuando",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cubrir",
    "back": "to cover",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to cover",
    "back": "cubrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cuerpo",
    "back": "body",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "body",
    "back": "cuerpo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "culpa",
    "back": "fault",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "fault",
    "back": "culpa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "cuna",
    "back": "crib",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "crib",
    "back": "cuna",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "decisión",
    "back": "decision",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "decision",
    "back": "decisión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "de inmediato",
    "back": "immediately",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "immediately",
    "back": "de inmediato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "de",
    "back": "of",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "of",
    "back": "de",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "de nuevo",
    "back": "again",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "again",
    "back": "de nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "de repente",
    "back": "suddenly",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "suddenly",
    "back": "de repente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "decorador",
    "back": "decorator",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "decorator",
    "back": "decorador",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "decorar",
    "back": "to decorate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to decorate",
    "back": "decorar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "delgado",
    "back": "slim",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "slim",
    "back": "delgado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "deporte",
    "back": "sport",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sport",
    "back": "deporte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "desayunar",
    "back": "to eat breakfast",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to eat breakfast",
    "back": "desayunar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "descansar",
    "back": "to rest",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to rest",
    "back": "descansar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "descubrir",
    "back": "to discover",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to discover",
    "back": "descubrir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "deseo",
    "back": "wish/desire",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "wish/desire",
    "back": "deseo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "despedido",
    "back": "fired",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "fired",
    "back": "despedido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "despierto",
    "back": "awake",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "awake",
    "back": "despierto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "después",
    "back": "after",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "after",
    "back": "después",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "devastado",
    "back": "devastated",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "devastated",
    "back": "devastado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "día",
    "back": "day",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "day",
    "back": "día",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "diez",
    "back": "ten",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "ten",
    "back": "diez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "diferente",
    "back": "different",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "different",
    "back": "diferente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "difícil",
    "back": "difficult",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "difficult",
    "back": "difícil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "dinero",
    "back": "money",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "money",
    "back": "dinero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "divertido",
    "back": "fun",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "fun",
    "back": "divertido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "doble",
    "back": "double",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "double",
    "back": "doble",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "domingo",
    "back": "Sunday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "Sunday",
    "back": "domingo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "donde",
    "back": "where",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "where",
    "back": "donde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "dos",
    "back": "two",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "two",
    "back": "dos",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ducharse",
    "back": "to shower",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to shower",
    "back": "ducharse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "dulce",
    "back": "sweet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sweet",
    "back": "dulce",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "dulces",
    "back": "sweets",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sweets",
    "back": "dulces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "durante",
    "back": "during",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "during",
    "back": "durante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "educado",
    "back": "polite",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "polite",
    "back": "educado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "egoísta",
    "back": "selfish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "selfish",
    "back": "egoísta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ejercicio",
    "back": "exercise",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "exercise",
    "back": "ejercicio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "embarazada",
    "back": "pregnant",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "pregnant",
    "back": "embarazada",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "empezar",
    "back": "to start",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to start",
    "back": "empezar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "empleado",
    "back": "employee",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "employee",
    "back": "empleado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "empresa",
    "back": "company",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "company",
    "back": "empresa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "encender",
    "back": "to turn on",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to turn on",
    "back": "encender",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "encontrar",
    "back": "to find",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to find",
    "back": "encontrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "enfadado",
    "back": "annoyed",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "annoyed",
    "back": "enfadado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "enorme",
    "back": "enormous",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "enormous",
    "back": "enorme",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "entender",
    "back": "to understand",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to understand",
    "back": "entender",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "entonces",
    "back": "then",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "then",
    "back": "entonces",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "entrar",
    "back": "to enter",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to enter",
    "back": "entrar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "entrenadora",
    "back": "trainer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "trainer",
    "back": "entrenadora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "equipo",
    "back": "team",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "team",
    "back": "equipo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "en serio",
    "back": "seriously",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "seriously",
    "back": "en serio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "esconder",
    "back": "to hide",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to hide",
    "back": "esconder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "espacio",
    "back": "space",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "space",
    "back": "espacio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "especialmente",
    "back": "especially",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "especially",
    "back": "especialmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "esperar",
    "back": "to wait",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to wait",
    "back": "esperar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "estar",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "estar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "estar en buena forma",
    "back": "to be in good shape",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to be in good shape",
    "back": "estar en buena forma",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "estudiar",
    "back": "to study",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to study",
    "back": "estudiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "excelente",
    "back": "excellent",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "excellent",
    "back": "excelente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "experiencia",
    "back": "experience",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "experience",
    "back": "experiencia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "explicar",
    "back": "to explain",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to explain",
    "back": "explicar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "extraño",
    "back": "strange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "strange",
    "back": "extraño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fácil",
    "back": "easy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "easy",
    "back": "fácil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "familia",
    "back": "family",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "family",
    "back": "familia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fantastico",
    "back": "fantastic",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "fantastic",
    "back": "fantastico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "favorito",
    "back": "favourite",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "favourite",
    "back": "favorito",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "happy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "happy",
    "back": "feliz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "finalmente",
    "back": "finally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "finally",
    "back": "finalmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fruta",
    "back": "fruit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "fruit",
    "back": "fruta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fuente",
    "back": "source",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "source",
    "back": "fuente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fuera",
    "back": "outside",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "outside",
    "back": "fuera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fuerte",
    "back": "strong",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "strong",
    "back": "fuerte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fumar",
    "back": "to smoke",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to smoke",
    "back": "fumar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "fútbol",
    "back": "football",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "football",
    "back": "fútbol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "futuro",
    "back": "future",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "future",
    "back": "futuro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gafas",
    "back": "glasses",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "glasses",
    "back": "gafas",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ganar",
    "back": "to gain/earn/win",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to gain/earn/win",
    "back": "ganar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "garaje",
    "back": "garage",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "garage",
    "back": "garaje",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gastar",
    "back": "to spend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to spend",
    "back": "gastar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "genial",
    "back": "great",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "great",
    "back": "genial",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gimnasio",
    "back": "gym",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "gym",
    "back": "gimnasio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "girar",
    "back": "to turn",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to turn",
    "back": "girar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "golpear",
    "back": "to hit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to hit",
    "back": "golpear",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gracias",
    "back": "thank you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "thank you",
    "back": "gracias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "grande",
    "back": "big",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "big",
    "back": "grande",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gratis",
    "back": "free",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "free",
    "back": "gratis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "grave",
    "back": "serious",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "serious",
    "back": "grave",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gritar",
    "back": "to shout",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to shout",
    "back": "gritar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "grupo",
    "back": "group",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "group",
    "back": "grupo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "guardián",
    "back": "security guard",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "security guard",
    "back": "guardián",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "gustar",
    "back": "to like",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to like",
    "back": "gustar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "habitación",
    "back": "bedroom",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bedroom",
    "back": "habitación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hablar",
    "back": "to speak/talk",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to speak/talk",
    "back": "hablar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hacer",
    "back": "to do/make",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to do/make",
    "back": "hacer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hasta",
    "back": "until",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "until",
    "back": "hasta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hay",
    "back": "there is",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "there is",
    "back": "hay",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hermano",
    "back": "brother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "brother",
    "back": "hermano",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hijo",
    "back": "son",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "son",
    "back": "hijo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "historia",
    "back": "story",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "story",
    "back": "historia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hola",
    "back": "hello",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "hello",
    "back": "hola",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "hora",
    "back": "hour",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "hour",
    "back": "hora",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "huevo",
    "back": "egg",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "egg",
    "back": "huevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "idea",
    "back": "idea",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ignorar",
    "back": "to ignore",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to ignore",
    "back": "ignorar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ilegal",
    "back": "illegal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "illegal",
    "back": "ilegal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "imaginación",
    "back": "imagination",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "imagination",
    "back": "imaginación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "importante",
    "back": "important",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "important",
    "back": "importante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "incidente",
    "back": "incident",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "incident",
    "back": "incidente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "incómodo",
    "back": "uncomfortable",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "uncomfortable",
    "back": "incómodo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "infierno",
    "back": "hell",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "hell",
    "back": "infierno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "inmediatamente",
    "back": "immediately",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "immediately",
    "back": "inmediatamente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "intentar",
    "back": "to try",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to try",
    "back": "intentar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "interesante",
    "back": "interesting",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "interesting",
    "back": "interesante",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "inútil",
    "back": "useless",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "useless",
    "back": "inútil",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "investigar",
    "back": "to investigate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to investigate",
    "back": "investigar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ir",
    "back": "to go",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to go",
    "back": "ir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "jardín",
    "back": "garden",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "garden",
    "back": "jardín",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "jefe",
    "back": "boss",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "boss",
    "back": "jefe",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "joven",
    "back": "young",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "young",
    "back": "joven",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "jugar",
    "back": "to play",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to play",
    "back": "jugar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "junto",
    "back": "together",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "together",
    "back": "junto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "justicia",
    "back": "justice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "justice",
    "back": "justicia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ladrón",
    "back": "thief",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "thief",
    "back": "ladrón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "lago",
    "back": "large",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "large",
    "back": "lago",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "largo",
    "back": "long",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "long",
    "back": "largo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "las afueras",
    "back": "the outskirts",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "the outskirts",
    "back": "las afueras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "leer",
    "back": "to read",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to read",
    "back": "leer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "levantarse",
    "back": "to get up",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to get up",
    "back": "levantarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "libro",
    "back": "book",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "book",
    "back": "libro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "limón",
    "back": "lemon",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "lemon",
    "back": "limón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "limpiar",
    "back": "to clean",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to clean",
    "back": "limpiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "llamar",
    "back": "to call",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to call",
    "back": "llamar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "llegar",
    "back": "to arrive",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to arrive",
    "back": "llegar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "llevar",
    "back": "to wear",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to wear",
    "back": "llevar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "lo siento",
    "back": "sorry",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sorry",
    "back": "lo siento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "loco",
    "back": "crazy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "crazy",
    "back": "loco",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "luego",
    "back": "then",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "then",
    "back": "luego",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "luz",
    "back": "light",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "light",
    "back": "luz",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "madre",
    "back": "mother",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "mother",
    "back": "madre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mal",
    "back": "bad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bad",
    "back": "mal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mañana",
    "back": "morning/tomorrow",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "morning/tomorrow",
    "back": "mañana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "manera",
    "back": "manner",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "manner",
    "back": "manera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "máquina",
    "back": "machine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "machine",
    "back": "máquina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "marrón",
    "back": "brown",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "brown",
    "back": "marrón",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mascota",
    "back": "pet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "pet",
    "back": "mascota",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "más",
    "back": "more",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "more",
    "back": "más",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "material",
    "back": "material",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "material",
    "back": "material",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mayor",
    "back": "elder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "elder",
    "back": "mayor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "médico",
    "back": "doctor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "doctor",
    "back": "médico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mejor",
    "back": "better",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "better",
    "back": "mejor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mes",
    "back": "month",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "month",
    "back": "mes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mesa",
    "back": "table",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "table",
    "back": "mesa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mientras",
    "back": "while",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "while",
    "back": "mientras",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "minuto",
    "back": "minute",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "minute",
    "back": "minuto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mirar",
    "back": "to look at/ to watch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to look at/ to watch",
    "back": "mirar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mismo",
    "back": "same",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "same",
    "back": "mismo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mitad",
    "back": "half",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "half",
    "back": "mitad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "montaña",
    "back": "mountain",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "mountain",
    "back": "montaña",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "montar",
    "back": "to ride/ to mount",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to ride/ to mount",
    "back": "montar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mucho",
    "back": "a lot",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "a lot",
    "back": "mucho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "mueble",
    "back": "furniture",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "furniture",
    "back": "mueble",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "muy",
    "back": "very",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "very",
    "back": "muy",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nadar",
    "back": "to swim",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to swim",
    "back": "nadar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nadie",
    "back": "nobody",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "nobody",
    "back": "nadie",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "necesario",
    "back": "necessary",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "necessary",
    "back": "necesario",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "necesitar",
    "back": "to need",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to need",
    "back": "necesitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "negro",
    "back": "black",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "black",
    "back": "negro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nepalí",
    "back": "Nepalese",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "Nepalese",
    "back": "nepalí",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nieto",
    "back": "grandchild",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "grandchild",
    "back": "nieto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ni siquiera",
    "back": "not even",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "not even",
    "back": "ni siquiera",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "noche",
    "back": "night",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "night",
    "back": "noche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "normalmente",
    "back": "normally",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "normally",
    "back": "normalmente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nosotros",
    "back": "us",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "us",
    "back": "nosotros",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "noticias",
    "back": "news",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "news",
    "back": "noticias",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "novia",
    "back": "girlfriend",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "girlfriend",
    "back": "novia",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nuestro",
    "back": "our",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "our",
    "back": "nuestro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nuevo",
    "back": "new",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "new",
    "back": "nuevo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nueve",
    "back": "nine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "nine",
    "back": "nueve",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "nunca",
    "back": "never",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "never",
    "back": "nunca",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "o",
    "back": "or",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "or",
    "back": "o",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ocho",
    "back": "eight",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "eight",
    "back": "ocho",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "odiar",
    "back": "to hate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to hate",
    "back": "odiar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ojo",
    "back": "eye",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "eye",
    "back": "ojo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "opinión",
    "back": "opinion",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "opinion",
    "back": "opinión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ordenar",
    "back": "to order",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to order",
    "back": "ordenar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ordenador",
    "back": "computer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "computer",
    "back": "ordenador",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "orgulloso",
    "back": "proud",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "proud",
    "back": "orgulloso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "otra vez",
    "back": "again",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "again",
    "back": "otra vez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "otro",
    "back": "other",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "other",
    "back": "otro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "padre",
    "back": "father",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "father",
    "back": "padre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "para",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "para",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "parecer",
    "back": "to seem",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to seem",
    "back": "parecer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pared",
    "back": "wall",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "wall",
    "back": "pared",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pantalla",
    "back": "screen",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "screen",
    "back": "pantalla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pasar",
    "back": "to spend/ to pass",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to spend/ to pass",
    "back": "pasar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pasatiempo",
    "back": "hobby",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "hobby",
    "back": "pasatiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pastel",
    "back": "cake",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cake",
    "back": "pastel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "película",
    "back": "film",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "film",
    "back": "película",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pelo",
    "back": "hair",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "hair",
    "back": "pelo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pensar",
    "back": "to think",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to think",
    "back": "pensar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pequeña",
    "back": "small",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "small",
    "back": "pequeña",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "perdida",
    "back": "waste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "waste",
    "back": "perdida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "periódico",
    "back": "newspaper",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "newspaper",
    "back": "periódico",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pero",
    "back": "but",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "but",
    "back": "pero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "perra",
    "back": "bitch",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "bitch",
    "back": "perra",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "persona",
    "back": "person",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "person",
    "back": "persona",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "piña",
    "back": "pineapple",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "pineapple",
    "back": "piña",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "piso",
    "back": "floor",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "floor",
    "back": "piso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "plato",
    "back": "plate",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "plate",
    "back": "plato",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "poder",
    "back": "to be able to",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to be able to",
    "back": "poder",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "policía",
    "back": "police",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "police",
    "back": "policía",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "polideportivo",
    "back": "sports centre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sports centre",
    "back": "polideportivo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ponerse",
    "back": "to put on",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to put on",
    "back": "ponerse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "por",
    "back": "for",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "for",
    "back": "por",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "por qué",
    "back": "why",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "why",
    "back": "por qué",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "por si acaso",
    "back": "just in case",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "just in case",
    "back": "por si acaso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "porque",
    "back": "because",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "because",
    "back": "porque",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "preguntar",
    "back": "to ask",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to ask",
    "back": "preguntar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "preocupado",
    "back": "worried",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "worried",
    "back": "preocupado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "preparar",
    "back": "to prepare",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to prepare",
    "back": "preparar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "presentimiento",
    "back": "feeling",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "feeling",
    "back": "presentimiento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "primero",
    "back": "first",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "first",
    "back": "primero",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "principal",
    "back": "principal/main",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "principal/main",
    "back": "principal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "problema",
    "back": "problem",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "problem",
    "back": "problema",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "pronto",
    "back": "soon",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "soon",
    "back": "pronto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "propio",
    "back": "own",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "own",
    "back": "propio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "próximo",
    "back": "next",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "next",
    "back": "próximo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "proyecto",
    "back": "project",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "project",
    "back": "proyecto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "puerta",
    "back": "door",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "door",
    "back": "puerta",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "qué",
    "back": "what",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "what",
    "back": "qué",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "qué tal",
    "back": "how are you",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "how are you",
    "back": "qué tal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "quién",
    "back": "who",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "who",
    "back": "quién",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "quejarse",
    "back": "to complain",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to complain",
    "back": "quejarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "querer",
    "back": "to want",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to want",
    "back": "querer",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "queso",
    "back": "cheese",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "cheese",
    "back": "queso",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "raro",
    "back": "strange",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "strange",
    "back": "raro",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "recuperar",
    "back": "recover",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "recover",
    "back": "recuperar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "reír",
    "back": "to laugh",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to laugh",
    "back": "reír",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "relejar",
    "back": "to relax",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to relax",
    "back": "relejar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "reputación",
    "back": "reputation",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "reputation",
    "back": "reputación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "retirarse",
    "back": "to retire",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to retire",
    "back": "retirarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "robar",
    "back": "to steal",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to steal",
    "back": "robar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "robo",
    "back": "robbery",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "robbery",
    "back": "robo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ropa",
    "back": "clothes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "clothes",
    "back": "ropa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "rubio",
    "back": "blonde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "blonde",
    "back": "rubio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ruido",
    "back": "noise",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "noise",
    "back": "ruido",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "rutina",
    "back": "routine",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "routine",
    "back": "rutina",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sábado",
    "back": "Saturday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "Saturday",
    "back": "sábado",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sábana",
    "back": "sheet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sheet",
    "back": "sábana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "saber",
    "back": "to know",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to know",
    "back": "saber",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sala",
    "back": "living room",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "living room",
    "back": "sala",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "salir",
    "back": "to go out",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to go out",
    "back": "salir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "salud",
    "back": "health",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "health",
    "back": "salud",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "saludar",
    "back": "to greet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to greet",
    "back": "saludar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "siete",
    "back": "seven",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "seven",
    "back": "siete",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "secreto",
    "back": "secret",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "secret",
    "back": "secreto",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "seis",
    "back": "six",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "six",
    "back": "seis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "semana",
    "back": "week",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "week",
    "back": "semana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sensación",
    "back": "sensation",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sensation",
    "back": "sensación",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sentir",
    "back": "to feel",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to feel",
    "back": "sentir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ser",
    "back": "to be",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to be",
    "back": "ser",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "serio",
    "back": "serious",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "serious",
    "back": "serio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "siempre",
    "back": "always",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "always",
    "back": "siempre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "silencio",
    "back": "silence",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "silence",
    "back": "silencio",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "silla",
    "back": "seat",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "seat",
    "back": "silla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "simplemente",
    "back": "simply",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "simply",
    "back": "simplemente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sin",
    "back": "without",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "without",
    "back": "sin",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sobre",
    "back": "over/about",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "over/about",
    "back": "sobre",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sol",
    "back": "sun",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sun",
    "back": "sol",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "solo",
    "back": "only",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "only",
    "back": "solo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sorpresa",
    "back": "surprise",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "surprise",
    "back": "sorpresa",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "su",
    "back": "his/her/theirs",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "his/her/theirs",
    "back": "su",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sueldo",
    "back": "salary",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "salary",
    "back": "sueldo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "sueño",
    "back": "dream",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "dream",
    "back": "sueño",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "suerte",
    "back": "luck",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "luck",
    "back": "suerte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "suficiente",
    "back": "sufficient",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sufficient",
    "back": "suficiente",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "talento",
    "back": "talent",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "talent",
    "back": "talento",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "también",
    "back": "as well",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "as well",
    "back": "también",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "techo",
    "back": "ceiling",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "ceiling",
    "back": "techo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "televisión",
    "back": "television",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "television",
    "back": "televisión",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tener",
    "back": "to have",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to have",
    "back": "tener",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tener que",
    "back": "to have to",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to have to",
    "back": "tener que",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tenis",
    "back": "tennis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "tennis",
    "back": "tenis",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "terminar",
    "back": "to finish",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to finish",
    "back": "terminar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tiempo",
    "back": "time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "time",
    "back": "tiempo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "todo",
    "back": "all",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "all",
    "back": "todo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tomar",
    "back": "to take",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to take",
    "back": "tomar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tortilla",
    "back": "Spanish omelette",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "Spanish omelette",
    "back": "tortilla",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajador",
    "back": "worker",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "worker",
    "back": "trabajador",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajar",
    "back": "to work",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to work",
    "back": "trabajar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "trabajo",
    "back": "work/job",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "work/job",
    "back": "trabajo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tranquilidad",
    "back": "tranquillity",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "tranquillity",
    "back": "tranquilidad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tranquilo",
    "back": "quiet",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "quiet",
    "back": "tranquilo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tres",
    "back": "three",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "three",
    "back": "tres",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "triste",
    "back": "sad",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "sad",
    "back": "triste",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "tunarse",
    "back": "to take turns",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to take turns",
    "back": "tunarse",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "turno",
    "back": "shift",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "shift",
    "back": "turno",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "turno de noche",
    "back": "night shift",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "night shift",
    "back": "turno de noche",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "único",
    "back": "only",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "only",
    "back": "único",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "vecino",
    "back": "neighbour",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "neighbour",
    "back": "vecino",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "veinte",
    "back": "twenty",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "twenty",
    "back": "veinte",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ventana",
    "back": "window",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "window",
    "back": "ventana",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "ver",
    "back": "to see",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "ver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "verde",
    "back": "green",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "green",
    "back": "verde",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "verdura",
    "back": "vegetable",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "vegetable",
    "back": "verdura",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "vez",
    "back": "time",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "time",
    "back": "vez",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "vida",
    "back": "life",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "life",
    "back": "vida",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "viernes",
    "back": "Friday",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "Friday",
    "back": "viernes",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "visitar",
    "back": "to visit",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to visit",
    "back": "visitar",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "vivir",
    "back": "to live",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to live",
    "back": "vivir",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "volver",
    "back": "to return",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "to return",
    "back": "volver",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "y",
    "back": "and",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "and",
    "back": "y",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "recognition",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Recognition",
    "front": "zumo",
    "back": "juice",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "recognition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "production",
    "deck": "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón::Production",
    "front": "juice",
    "back": "zumo",
    "tags": [
      "vocabulary",
      "Short Spanish Stories A1::5 - El Albañil y El Ladrón",
      "production"
    ]
  }
]